

## CONTACT

jclscoates@gmail.com

(480) 490-1925

Phoenix, Arizona

# Lauren Coates

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN,

Greetings! I hope this letter finds you well.

In the past I have achieved many goals at an exceptional rate. I have equipped myself with skills such as compliance, collaboration, teamwork, critical and analytical thinking, mentoring, negotiation, written and verbal communication, and loyalty. I am a quick study and teamplayer who loves to try new things. My experiences have developed many skills: multitasking, decision making, perfecting flexibility and adaptability, to name a few.

I have the passion and drive that will benefit a team and profit your company when given the opportunity to collaborate. Thank you for your time and consideration. Please reach out at any time should you have further questions. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

Sincerely,

**Lauren Coates** 

# Lauren Coates

jclscoates@gmail.com (480)490-1925

#### **EDUCATION**

**2011-2012 – Associates in Arts degree-** Green River Community College.

2014-2016 – Bachelor's Degree – Major in University Studies with a Minor in Psychology- BYU-Idaho June 2024-Current (ends November 2024) BootCamp - Full stack web development bootcamp through ASU

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Bankruptcy/State Court Collector III**

May 2023-Present

- o Manage state court email for the Bankruptcy State Court team at Arizona Department of Revenue
- o Produce timely responses to all Attorney General requests
- Conduct compliance checks for bankruptcy cases
- Prepare cases for liens
- o Train new hires on operational procedures
- Create and facilitate team meetings
- Scan and prepare bankruptcy correspondence for our team
- Compose and update various forms of data for the Attorney General's office
- Organize and execute open and close reports for cases with the attorney general office
- o Call banks and employers for updated levy status
- o Receive and answer department phone line
- Collaborated on a special project reducing the Collection teams backlog

#### Stay at Home Mother

September 2017-Present

- o Maintain Busy Household
- Set and adhere to budget
- o Organize and educate children

#### **Store Owner/Creator- Etsy**

August 2022- present

- o Create Artwork for resale
- Manage professional website, package and ship orders
- Created logo and font for a unique store front

#### Personal Assistant – Edelmayer & Sons, Inc.

March 2016- February 2017

- o Maintained schedules
- Cleaned and Kept Professional and Personal environment
- Managed Correspondence

#### Sushi Chef/Server - Dong's Sushi

September 2015-April 2016

- o Managed multiple customer orders simultaneously to each customers satisfaction
- o Efficiently cooked, fried, and cleaned to decrease wait time for customers
- o Frequently adapted to different roles according to the constantly changing needs of the restaurant

# Lauren Coates

jclscoates@gmail.com (480)490-1925

### Merchandiser-CAF Outdoor Cleaning Solutions, Inc.

#### 2011-2012

- Packaged inventory
- Inventory accountability
- o Scheduled and oversaw deliveries and pick-ups
- o Prepared samples

### **AWARDS/COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT**

2007-2011 - Lead Ballerina- Evergreen City Ballet Company

2009-2010 - DECA Club-Winner of the Business Services Marketing Series

2013-2014 - Full time Missionary- The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints

2015-present - Sunday School Teacher

### **SKILLS**

**Exceptional Customer Service Skills** 

Professional Written and Verbal Communication

**Statistical Reporting** 

Sales & Time Management Skills

**Excellent Conflict Resolution Skills** 

HTML

JavaScript

SQL .

NodeJS

Critical Thinking Skills/Multi-Tasking

**Problem Solving Solutions** 

Microsoft Suite: Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook

Google Suite: Gmail, Meet, Chat, Drive, Sheets, Docs, and Forms

Procreate

CSS

TypeScript

TAS (Tax Accounting System)

React